https://www.hsco.org/privacy-policy/

Our Locations
HSCO Shelter: 61170 S.E. 27th St. Bend, OR  97702 541/382-3537 Open M-F 10am-5:30pm Saturday 10am-5pm Closed Sundays & major holidays
HSCO Thrift Store: 61220 S. Highway 97 Bend, OR  97702 541/329-7637 Open Every Day 10am-6pm Donations Accepted: Mon., Wed., Fri. 10am-5pm Schedule a Furniture Pickup
Bend Spay & Neuter Clinic: 910 SE Wilson, Ste A1 Bend, Oregon 97702 541/617-1010 Surgery: Wednesday: 7:30am to 5pm Thursday: 7:30am to 5pm Friday: 7:30am to 5pm Vaccine & Microchip Clinic: Saturday: 9am-2pm Closed Sunday & Monday
HSCO Privacy Notice
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for www.hsco.org. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following:
What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be
What choices are available to you regarding the use of your
The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your
How you can correct any inaccuracies in the
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
Your Access to and Control Over Information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:
See what data we have about you, if
Change/correct any data we have about
Have us delete any data we have about
Express any concern you have about our use of your
Security
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.
Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 541-382-3537 or via email at info@hsco.org
HSCO Privacy Notice
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for www.hsco.org. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following:
What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be
What choices are available to you regarding the use of your
The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your
How you can correct any inaccuracies in the
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
Your Access to and Control Over Information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:
See what data we have about you, if
Change/correct any data we have about
Have us delete any data we have about
Express any concern you have about our use of your
Security
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.
Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 541-382-3537 or via email at info@hsco.org
Our Locations
HSCO Shelter: 61170 S.E. 27th St. Bend, OR  97702 541/382-3537 Open M-F 10am-5:30pm Saturday 10am-5pm Closed Sundays & major holidays
HSCO Thrift Store: 61220 S. Highway 97 Bend, OR  97702 541/329-7637 Open Every Day 10am-6pm Donations Accepted: Mon., Wed., Fri. 10am-5pm Schedule a Furniture Pickup
Bend Spay & Neuter Clinic: 910 SE Wilson, Ste A1 Bend, Oregon 97702 541/617-1010 Surgery: Wednesday: 7:30am to 5pm Thursday: 7:30am to 5pm Friday: 7:30am to 5pm Vaccine & Microchip Clinic: Saturday: 9am-2pm Closed Sunday & Monday
Sign up to get HSCO news and updates delivered straight to your inbox.
Join Our Email List
For Email Marketing you can trust.
